best for the day of the day.
Father, I just, I'm really thankful for giving me the honor to be able to pray for our
city leaders.
But I pray that's each and every person that is in a leadership position would understand that
it's a God given authority.
But I pray that they would just use that authority to honor you and to bring my and let
you do place.
Father, we thank you for them.
And Lord, I pray that each and every member of this city would just honor them as a God
appointed authority.
I pray a blessing over them and declare this in the name of Jesus.
Amen.
To the flag of the United States of America.
To the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, individual, with liberty and justice for our honor.
Thank you, Pastor.
Thank you.
Thank you, Father.
Four of us, again, go to the personal practice.
Five planes list.
Make motion, we approve.
Second.
Hi.
Lawrence.
I.
Dylan.
Don't go over.
I.
Six.
May.)
Me.
August 5th.
2025, raise the meeting.
Most.
and they amount of $12,570 in the 70s, and so this is claims that our students on their own.
This is for professional services, for name and try to remain.
I'm $12,570 in dollars.
I'm happy to give this to this guest.
We went over the $740,000, but if these two claims are approved,
our total over the $740 would be $62,200, $33.50.
So this was money we had in the professional services account,
we needed that we were going to be really close with week that we had.
People can't slow it, so it's been a lot of some of the things.
Second.
So full cost.
Each set.
Jones.
Furns.
I'm Parker.
Hi.
Hey, you know, Straton Edmunds, and Boner playing for Pimps Gold,
of the RDA, we're live seeing the Associated Complaint,
for seeing this amount of $180.
Oh yes, but we're this is the same thing.
You know, Straton Edmunds is $180.
I'm like a set of no one goes to that negative 60,000 to 23,000 to 23,000.
For you?
For, I, so will.
Hi.
He's up.
Jo's.
Hi.
Parker.
There it looks like it's, uh, you got a run up in here.
And I'm also mastered grain from professional services, authorizing trust, manager or
it is the need design.
Yes, this is, uh, we're just asking for, read and prove them.
So we can use them to professional services they have done.
Jones, Tyrant's, he's said.
Hi.
Local, hi.
Parker.
Hi.
Dan, work order 25-1 with owes of engineering
for waterline utility relocation.
Located on the industrial parkway,
start state highway six and on a, between eight
drives trout, and buffalo run boulevard,
not in C44,843 dollars.
Eight, four, four, a thousand, eight,
and a hundred, four, three dollars.
Well, the housing trust manager,
for his doesn't need a sign.
Yes.
You said it again.
This is not their own 69-8,
but they're doing it like me.
And they've already agreed to,
no doubt, agreed to reimburse this for this.
This will be, who are you approved this once?
Not this, this is an 69.
Could we further, further north, by a tune in there?
Yeah, there were four, four, four, four, four,
four, four, three, five, and a project that run from
to change the 69.
Yeah, to the, yeah, all right.
It is even confusing for us, and it's even confusing for us.
This one fixed that issue, and that they had out of Buffalo
room with shut off out there at the edge of their property.
Oh, water, yes, the twin, yeah, between this and, yeah.
It would connect, the two, it would be awesome.
Yeah, like they're not the end of the line, yeah,
which would be really good.
I got no dodge point for it.
They already signed the list for the engineering part of it yet,
but the motion to approve.
This is okay.
It's so cool.
Hi.
Two side, bar and side, Parker.
Thank you.
11 more, or 25, that's two, with all the engineering,
for full attachment management package,
authorized transmitter, or it does move side.
Yes.
This is what I brought you back here.
Meeting your two-view, and it's about a plan for what
survey, and make sure that we want to attach to our polls,
that they're attaching the way we want them to attach to them,
and that they don't affect the lines.
It will just allow.
I mean, it's that change something.
Mr. Zalconi in the process for the five or two?
Well, pointing it up for the five or two.
Well, if anybody else wanted to hang,
say there's a new company that wanted to hang private,
they would have to go through this process
to make sure that we would be exempt ourselves.
This is just for who's already attached to our polls.
Yes, I'm sorry.
And then also, there's some conflict,
or clearance is not like that.
That we responsible to do that.
They actually have to be responsible for paying
for the construction cost to make it.
Right.
There's done included the beef schedule for a bullet action, right?
This is not included.
Peace schedule for that.
There is a schedule in there for what those inspections
and what their services are.
That we could be approving also.
There's a portion of that that we would be paying for that.
It references a bullet judgment.
We're a right amount.
I'm sorry, I don't know what I'm going to talk about it tonight.
All this information is already mapped on our GIS, though, isn't it?
Most of our polls are primary polls involved in.
We personally announced it when I went to each poll
and the GPS, DIS.
But with this, the difference in this is what they would want
but on there, we just check for loading on it and say,
and clearance is between, that we're wrong way.
Let's get from the other utilities, and make sure it's not free for all
but if it's just doing what they want to do.
Not a poll question tonight.
Yeah.
We'll make a motion we approve.
E7, don't go ahead.
Jones, hi.
Far and hi, Parker.
Hi.
12.
Work, rather than authorization, three dash, 20, 25, with own engineering,
for well number seven and DIS inspection,
construction, administration, inspection,
not exceed 100, $45,000, $700.
So this is for the inspections and inside visits
in for the new water tower.
This is at the price that I bring you here, of that price, is worst case scenario.
There are some money in there to be kept, some of the inspections stuff that we may be able to cut out for.
I actually talk to people that currently do our inspections on all our powers and tanks today,
and they actually would be willing to do free service too.
There's a paint inspection that they have in it.
It's pretty expensive, and what we're going to waste is that we can do that in house and not have to go out with that.
But we had this, we just wanted to get this presented to you, that tank starts.
We can go out to inspect and we'll see if there's a lot of that taking away house.
Does this end of the triangle?
Is it going to be just a straight up down?
It'd be, yes, it worked.
Like to went out on this.
Similar to what it was.
Yeah.
I told you about our project.
We did it one up there.
That's where it's somewhere around.
Is that what the new one's going to be?
That's exactly the word my head is going to be.
That's my exact word.
That's a great idea.
There's a...
It's a present.
It really, really costs it to paint right next to the tarmac.
I guess because it sounds like he's all said to my other places.
Close in the tarmac, you said?
Do I?
Yeah, it's right next to the tarmac.
Just like you said, not closing.
No.
They're painting it, so they have to build a containment area around it.
So they're painting it.
So they have to build a containment area.
They're painting it.
They're touching it across the paint.
Well, they never wanted to.
Because a lot of people got painted on their cars.
They didn't want to.
Motion to prove.
Second.
Double.
Time.
for the first time.
Thank you.
13 resolution.
MSU A in 2025-06, a meeting right away, excavation requirement.
So, this is something we're actually not going to vote on tonight or the ordinance, but
this we want to talk about it next week.
So, we've been working on this one with the interview months occurred.
We've got what Penny Speak, that does like a lot of the right ways to pull a touch on
the stuff and everything.
So, our current ordinance, we had, does not have a lot of teeth in it.
So, we've been at the end of so that's what it did to put teeth in it to allow us to do better
regularly.
Like, well, I just have a permit for people to dig in right away, and now we'll actually
let them have them have a bond.
Like, at 200, that we talked about today, 200,000 dollar bond.
So, that way, you know, they leave it a mess and we can collect it on their bond.
I don't know.
I have a whole attachment agreement with, well, we'll be a part of the ordinance, but it will come and
follow in right after the ordinance that allows us to charge like what the current rate is.
And it will be a part attachment.
You know, you need to charge for attachment, not just for a poll.
I mean, I think we charge, we're from $2 to $6.00 a poll.
And she's saying they're going right right now.
It's like $13 a poll.
So, obviously, we're, you know, right behind.
So, I mean, this is like, I got to get the board updated.
We, we were glad for it tonight, but there's something that we went back and forth on.
We kind of brought one of some more teeth.
Let's say how many comes in and they want to, and other gas companies come in and
want to forget that.
I don't know if I can know how is it where we want to have teeth developed, like,
hold them accountable for the damage that they do.
I'm trying to think, what else do we have?
When there's something else that we can listen to, it's not even just the company,
but then you would either they serve to that company.
Yes, they have to be registered to say that we're going to have their insurance on file.
Because I know, like, as utility director, we got lots of calls, because, you know,
and bus is one of them off as AT&T.
You could let you run somebody's yard.
Everybody thinks it's a city.
We'll now all right now.
We're there.
So, it's just a total more teeth than it was we were excited about.
It's good.
Just kind of a part attachment.
It's really big because, again, in my former life, I left a few.
And people leave trash on our home.
We do the AT&T.
We're going to take stuff off.
We're going to get charged for it.
There'll be a lot of junk on the phone.
There'll be a lot of playoffs and screws.
It shouldn't have been there.
What are our guys going to climb one?
That's in their way.
It's dangerous.
So, we're really excited about it.
I mean, we wanted to be as best we can.
We can't pray for it.
That's why it was put on next weeks.
There was a couple of Thanksgiving night.
We're going back and forth on a misty today.
You've ever been rash, right?
14.
That a new business.
If any, which is a residence in close to your visit,
in the 10th of April.
I have a question about one of the reports in here.
On the pollution control.
On the second page of the top, it talks about it.
We're going back and forth.
That's really old and worn out. Is that something that's going to be very costly to replace?
Yeah, well, I know a little bit about it, so that's why I brought it up.
So what's our plan if that thing fails like before we're getting ready to have a session where we can approve an emergency?
Is there redundancy?
Okay, that's really kind of what my question was because we're into a case where you've got to spend a lot of money and it's an emergency, things can get weird.
Okay, it's all I had.
Sorry.
Okay.